(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE
Rock Festa!!!
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
IRyS
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
AZKi
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
猫汰つな
Nekota Tsuna
あぁ 呆れだす粗暴に
Ah, disgusted by the coarseness.
差し替えられた
Replaced,
現存に掛かった固定解答
the fixed answer weighing on my existence.
反則じみた応えじゃ
With an answer that borders on a foul,
見透かされてしまうな
I'll surely be seen through.
この道を渡りきっても
Even if I make it across this road,
まだ視界は 曇っている
my vision is still cloudy.
履き替えた 大人になってから
Since I changed shoes and became an adult,
縮みきった 歩幅と感情
my stride and emotions have shriveled.
削れだした 身体に対して
To my body that has started to wear down,
「気付け」と 唄ってる
it's singing, "Wake up."
はみ出した 心じゃ
With a heart that has overflowed,
居られないのならさ
if I can no longer stay here,
染み付いた この青さを
this blueness that has stained me,
切り離して しまっていい?
can I just cut it off?
ずっと 語りかけてた日々を
The days that spoke to me for so long,
嘆くように
as if in lament.
「深い闇に飲み込まれないよう」って
"Don't get swallowed by the deep darkness."
染まりきった 現実に
In this completely dyed reality,
答えなんてない
there is no answer.
逃げ出してしまった
I ran away.
言葉を羽織って
Cloaked in words,
溶けだした 心を
my melted heart,
胸に隠している
I hide it within my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を
My body, completely chilled,
騙すように
as if to deceive it,
描きかけた いつかの枯れた夢を
I trace the withered dream I once began to draw,
なぞっている
going over it again.
あぁ 暴れだす 言葉に
Ah, in the rampaging words.
差し替えられた
Replaced,
幻想に掛かった固定概念と
the stereotypes trapped in the illusion.
止まった理想じゃ
With a stagnant ideal,
見透かされてしまうな
I'll surely be seen through.
この道を渡りきっても
Even if I make it across this road,
まだ次回だ 続いていく
it's just 'next time' again, it goes on.
履き違えた 大人になってから
Since I became a mistaken adult,
尖りだした 思いの回想
recollections of sharpened thoughts.
ずっと 見えなくなった足跡
The footprints that disappeared long ago,
探している
I am searching for them.
はみ出した 心じゃ
With a heart that has overflowed,
居られないのならさ
if I can no longer stay here,
澄みきった この青さを
this completely clear blueness,
曝け出して しまっていい?
is it okay to expose it all?
ずっと 語りかけてた日々を
The days that spoke to me for so long,
隠すように
as if to hide them.
「深い闇に飲み込まれないよう」って
"Don't get swallowed by the deep darkness."
決まりきった 現実に
In this predetermined reality,
答えなんていらない
I don't need an answer.
逃げ出してしまった
I ran away.
言葉を羽織って
Cloaked in words,
溶けだした 心を
my melted heart,
胸に隠している
I hide it within my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を
My body, completely chilled,
騙すように
as if to deceive it,
描きかけた いつかの枯れた夢を
I trace the withered dream I once began to draw,
なぞっている
going over it again.
あぁ 錆び付いてる
Ah, it is rusting.
今をただ 不安定に立つ
Standing unstably in the present.
裏返る脳裏に
In my inverted mind,
汚されてしまったあの日達
those days were sullied.
願っては 辿ってた
I wished for them and pursued them,
手放してしまったのに
even though I let them go.
逃げ出してしまった
I ran away.
言葉を羽織って
Cloaked in words,
溶けだした 心を
my melted heart,
胸に隠している
I hide it within my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を
My body, completely chilled,
騙すように
as if to deceive it,
描きかけた いつかの枯れた夢を
I trace the withered dream I once began to draw,
なぞっている
going over it again.
Can't get away when I try to explain
Nothing comes out along with my expectation
I must play and act your feeling
Breathing, I gotta change this relation
アダルトな着ぐるみ着てる僕
I'm wearing an adult-sized costume suit.
心はいつも不安定 天秤シーソー
My heart is always an unstable seesaw balance.
まさかの発言で孤立化する
Isolated by an unexpected remark.
色眼鏡越し彷徨う僕
I wander through the view of colored glasses.
今日も今この瞬間に腹が立つ
Even today, right now, this moment makes me angry.
言葉がいつも後ろ髪引く
Words are always holding me back.
全部ダメダメなんでしょ？
Everything is no good, right?
じゃあもう放っといて
Then just leave me alone.
ハナからなかったことにしよう
Let's pretend it never happened from the start.
ラリルラリラリラ
La-li-lu-la-li-la-li-la.
それじゃダメダメ
That won't do, no good.
悪い癖だね もうしない
It's a bad habit, I won't do it anymore.
どうせ嫌われているなら 食い気味でいこう
If I'm going to be hated anyway, let's be aggressive.
何もかもが暗く黒く見える
Everything looks dark and black.
色眼鏡付きのアダルトなパチモンスーツ
An adult-sized knockoff suit with colored glasses.
必殺技かけるゼロで全部
My special move multiplied by zero equals everything.
消し去ってやろうか 強気な僕
Shall I wipe it all away? My strong-willed self asks.
だけど実際はやっぱ溺死したいの
But in reality, I actually want to drown.
身軽さ奪われ動けない
Robbed of my agility, I can't move.
それでもいい子とバランスとれてるんだよ
Even so, I'm keeping a balance with being a 'good kid'.
君は耳元でそれを言う
You whisper that right into my ear.
それにしちゃ少しあんまりじゃない？
Considering that, isn't it a bit too much?
ていうか不公平じゃない？
Or rather, isn't that unfair?
どうせ勝ち目なんてないし
There's no chance of winning anyway.
食い気味でいこう
Let's be aggressive.
I feel this moment
No one can take it
そんなん会だって 伝わらなけりゃ意味ないないないの
Even a meeting like that means nothing if it doesn't get across.
今日も今この瞬間が大事なの
Today too, this very moment is what's important.
奪う権利はあなた方にはない
You people don't have the right to steal it.
全部ダメダメ
Everything is no good.
何がダメダメなんでしょ？
What exactly is no good?
なあ 納得いくまで話してよ
Hey, explain it until I'm satisfied.
どうせ屁理屈並べるんならバカみたい
It looks stupid if you're just going to list quibbles anyway.
トドメを刺す気でいるなら
If you intend to deliver the finishing blow,
今がチャンスだぞ
now is your chance!
はーい！Yeah！ということで...
Haaai! Yeeeah! So...
こやっぴー！常闇トワ様です。
Koyappi! I am Tokoyami Towa-sama.
はい！ということで、なんと...
Yes! So, surprisingly...
本日6周年を迎えました！
Today marks my 6th anniversary!
イェーイ！6... 6？
Yaaay! Six... Six?
悪魔の数字「6」？
The devil's number 'six'?
ということは今年はトワちゃんの年ということでもいいでしょうか？
Does that mean it's okay to say this is Towa-chan's year?
ま、よくないか。いいか。
Well, maybe not. Or is it okay?
ま、人によってはトワちゃんの...
Well, for some people...
ね、あの年しにしたっていいということで。
you know, it's fine to make it Towa-chan's year.
はい、よろしくお願いします！
Yes, please treat me well!
常闇トワ6周年記念ライブでよろしくお願いします！
It's Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live! Let's do this!
目指せトレンド入り！
Aiming for trending!
えー、そしてね、えー、この後はね、いろんな告知もありますので
And well, there will be various announcements after this...
最後まで見ていってくれればなと思います！
So I hope you'll watch until the end!
はい
Yes.
えー、で今日なんですけれども
So, about today...
えー、1月3日となっておりまして
It is January 3rd.
えー、世の中はお休みの日ということで
Since the world is on holiday...
えー、わたくしも休みの日ということで
And since I am also on holiday...
えー、本日のライブは全編収録となっております！
Today's live is entirely pre-recorded!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you for your understanding!
そして
And then...
えー、この後はなんとゲストパート！
After this is the guest part!
いっぱい、いろんなね、ゲストが出てくれるので
Lots of different guests will be appearing...
楽しんで見ていってくれればなと思います！
So I hope you enjoy watching!
では
Well then...
ゲストパート、どうぞ！
Guest part, here we go!
闇を駆け抜けて どこへ向かう
Racing through the darkness, where do we go?
月明かりだけが ただ一つの道標
Only the moonlight is our single guidepost.
痛みも悲しみも 拭いきれず
Unable to wipe away the pain and sadness,
されどこの胸の 炎は消させない
Yet I won't let the fire in this chest be extinguished.
誰が為に僕たちは この想いを貫いて
For whose sake do we pierce through with these feelings?
闇を裂き 日の下で
Tearing through the darkness, under the sun,
光射す日まで
Until the day light shines.
解き放たれた
Unleashed,
心に宿した火を
The fire dwelling in my heart.
舞い上げ纏え 今
Soar up and clad yourself in it, now,
夜明けの向こう側へ
To the other side of the dawn.
君がいるこの世界
This world where you exist,
もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love it once more.
我が命 果てようとも
Even if my life should end,
繋いで行こう
Let's connect and go on,
絆が紡いで
Woven by bonds,
生まれた奇跡を
The miracle that was born.
喜怒哀楽 夢揺らめいてる
Emotions and dreams are wavering,
写し世
In this transient world.
互いの正義を また繰り返し
Repeating each other's justice again,
振りかざす
Brandishing it.
誰が為に繋ぐ命
For whose sake is life connected?
交わりもつれる運命
Fates that cross and tangle.
蛇の道 数多の罪
The path of the snake, numerous sins,
全て薙ぎ払え
Mow them all down!
解き放て 今
Unleash it, now!
僕らが起こした火を
The fire we ignited.
舞い上げ走れば
If we soar up and run,
明日が変わるはず
Tomorrow should change.
君といるこの世界
This world where I am with you,
二度と離さずに
Never letting go again.
君と共に往く
I will go with you.
瞼を閉じても
Even if I close my eyes,
思い出すあの陽を
I remember that sun.
打ちのめされても
Even if beaten down,
焦がれた未来を
The future we yearned for.
いつの日か君に
One day, to you,
捧げてみせよう
I will dedicate it.
解き放たれた
Unleashed,
心に宿した火を
The fire dwelling in my heart.
舞い上げ纏え 今
Soar up and clad yourself in it, now,
夜明けの向こうへ
To beyond the dawn.
解き放て 今
Unleash it, now!
僕らが起こした火を
The fire we ignited.
舞い上げ走れば
If we soar up and run,
明日が変わるはず
Tomorrow should change.
君がいたこの世界
This world where you were,
もう一度愛せるまで
Until I can love it once more.
我が命 果てようとも
Even if my life should end,
繋げていくよ
I will connect it.
絆が紡いで
Woven by bonds,
生まれた奇跡を
The miracle that was born.
抱きしめられた記憶から
From the memories of being held,
流れ出た赤い雫
Flowed red drops.
人様に見せるものじゃないの
It's not something to show others.
伝えたかった言葉が
The words I wanted to convey
もう一つの私になって
Became another version of me,
体の内側で何かを叫んでる
Screaming something from inside my body.
あぁ 欲しかったのに
Ah, even though I wanted it...
悔しかったのに
Even though I was frustrated...
ダメだよ 全部隠しておくの
It's no good, I have to hide it all.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
Because one person being sad is enough,
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
And I don't want to become any uglier than this.
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Without being found by anyone inside me,
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
You've been crying until you turned this color.
綺麗よ
It's beautiful.
私零れた心から
From my spilled heart,
流れ出た青い雫
Flowed blue drops.
人様に見せるものじゃないの
It's not something to show others.
あぁ ずっと孤独を飲み込んで
Ah, always swallowing loneliness,
遠くの海 底に沈んで
Sinking to the bottom of a distant sea,
そのまま宝石にでもなれるのを待つ
Waiting to become a jewel just like that.
Wow...
本当は嘘で飾って
Actually decorating with lies,
どこか満てない暮らしで慰めて
Consoling myself with a life unfulfilled somewhere.
誰かの悲劇で自分の悲劇を癒やして
Healing my own tragedy with someone else's tragedy.
悔しさに溺れた瞬間のままで
Staying in the moment drowned in frustration,
息もできずただ愛してるの
I just love you, unable to even breathe.
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
Because one person being sad is enough,
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
And I don't want to become any uglier than this.
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Without being found by anyone inside me,
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
You've been crying until you turned this color.
綺麗よ
It's beautiful.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ねえ 綺麗よ
Hey, it's beautiful.
片っぽで丸を作って
Make a loop with one end,
しっかり持ってて
Hold it tight.
もう片っぽでその丸の後ろを
With the other end, go behind that loop,
ぐるっと回って
Go all the way around.
間にできたポッケに入って
Go into the pocket made in between,
出てくるの待ってて
Wait for it to come out.
出てきたところを迎えにきた
I came to meet it where it came out.
せーので引っ張って
Pull on the count of three.
はじめはなんとも
At first, it's nothing special,
情けない形だとしても
Even if the shape looks pathetic.
同じだけ力を込めて
Put in the same amount of strength.
羽根は大きく
Make the wings big,
結び目は固く
Make the knot tight.
なるようにきつく
As tight as it can be,
結んでいてほしいの
I want you to keep it tied.
腕はここに
Your arm right here,
想い出は遠くに
Memories far away.
置いて置いて
Leave them behind,
ほしいの
I want you to.
片っぽでも引っ張っちゃえば ほどけちゃうけど
If I pull just one end, it will unravel, but...
作ったもの壊すのは 遥かに簡単だけど
It's far easier to destroy something you've made, but...
だけどほどく時も そうちゃんと 同じようにね
But when we untie it, let's do it properly, just the same way.
分かってるよ
I know.
でもできたらね せーので引っ張って
But if we can, let's pull it together on the count of three.
ほどけやしないようにと願って 力込めては
Praying it won't come undone, I put all my strength into it.
広げすぎた羽根に
With wings spread too wide,
戸惑う
I feel bewildered.
羽根は大きく
Make the wings big,
結び目は固く
and the knot tight.
なるようにきつく 結んでいて
Tie it strictly so it becomes that way.
ほしいの
I want you to.
夢はここに
Dreams are here,
思い出は遠くに
and memories are far away.
日付はそこにあるくらいがいい
It's better if the date is just simply there.
黙って引っ張ったりしないでよ
Don't pull on it silently.
不格好な蝶にしないでよ
Don't turn it into a misshapen butterfly.
結んだつもりが ほどいてたり
Thinking we tied it, we were untying it,
緩めたつもりが 締めていたり
Thinking we loosened it, we were tightening it.
この蒼くて広い世界に
In this pale and vast world,
無数に散らばった中から
from among the countless scattered pieces,
別々に二人選んだ糸を
the threads we each chose separately,
お互い手繰り寄せ合ったんだ
we reeled them in towards each other.
結ばれたんじゃなく 結んだんだ
We weren't tied together; we tied it ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
We pulled it together on the count of three.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように
So it wouldn't become too big or too small,
力を込めたんだ
we put our strength into it.
この蒼くて広い世界に
In this pale and vast world,
無数に散らばった中から
from among the countless scattered pieces,
別々に二人選んだ糸を
the threads we each chose separately,
お互い手繰り寄せ合ったんだ
we reeled them in towards each other.
結ばれたんじゃなく 結んだんだ
We weren't tied together; we tied it ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
We pulled it together on the count of three.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように
So it wouldn't become too big or too small,
力を込めたんだ
we put our strength into it.
陰にそっと隠れるのがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to just hide softly in the shadows?
蕾のような花だってあんじゃない
There are flowers that are like buds, aren't there?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず 華麗に咲いてる
Blooming magnificently without being disturbed by anyone.
甘い苦いにハマんない
Don't get caught up in sweet or bitter.
その判断がくだんない
Those judgments are worthless.
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't worry yourself sick and look down.
愛になれちゃいない
You haven't gotten used to love.
無駄に飾らない
Don't decorate yourself needlessly.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
A beautifully prepared vase,
肥やしもなにもいらない
fertilizer, or anything else—you don't need them.
その姿が美しい
That figure of yours is beautiful.
花になって
Become a flower.
ほら右左に笑って
Look, smile to the right and left.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
That face gives me chills, I can't look away.
味見して
Have a taste.
君の毒は私の薬って
Your poison is my medicine,
包んであげた
I wrapped it up for you.
愛帯 逢いたい 逢いたい その笑顔に
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see that smile.
愛帯 逢いたい 逢いたいと言えば 笑ってくれるかな
If I say I want to see you, I wonder if you'll smile for me.
取り殺させるくらいはいいじゃない
Being haunted to death sounds fine, doesn't it?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみせたい
If I'm being greedy, I want to make it bloom with these hands.
病のように
Like a sickness.
心は喰らう花
The heart is a devouring flower.
枯らしたないのさ
I don't want to let it wither.
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach,
水をあげ続けるから
I'll keep giving it water.
いい加減に気付いて
Realize it already,
君は素敵って
that you are wonderful.
自惚れてもっとお大事に
Be more conceited, take care of yourself.
無自覚なまま愛を蓄えて
Accumulating love while remaining unaware,
綺麗にされた花瓶も
even the cleaned vase,
肥やしもなにもいらない
doesn't need fertilizer or anything.
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly in that form.
花になって
Become a flower.
ほらニヒルに笑って その顔に
Look, laugh cynically, at that face.
ぞくぞくして目が離せない
I'm shivering and can't look away.
味見して 君の毒は私の薬って
Taste it, your poison is my medicine.
包んであげるから
I'll wrap you up in it.
楽にして 君の闇は私の光って
Relax, your darkness is my light.
愛してあげるから
I'll love you.
笑って
Smile.
多分 私じゃなくていいね
Probably, it doesn't have to be me.
余裕のない二人だったし
We were two people with no room to spare.
気付けば喧嘩ばっかりしてさ ごめんね
Before I knew it, we were just fighting. I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I've been meaning to talk for a while.
きっと私たち合わないね
We probably just don't match.
二人きりしかいない部屋でさ
In a room with just the two of us,
貴方ばっかり話していたよね
you were the only one talking, weren't you?
もしいつか何処かで会えたら
If we happen to meet somewhere again someday,
今日の事を笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll laugh about today.
理由もちゃんと話せないけれど
I can't really explain the reason properly, but
貴方が眠った後に泣くのは嫌
I hate crying after you've fallen asleep.
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness,
全部全部 嫌いじゃないの
I don't hate any of it, none of it.
ドライフラワーみたい
Like a dry flower,
君との日々も きっときっときっときっと
my days with you will surely, surely, surely, surely...
色褪せる
fade in color.
多分 君じゃなくてよかった
Maybe I'm glad it wasn't you.
もう泣かされることもないし
I won't be made to cry anymore,
「私ばかり」なんて言葉もなくなった
and the phrase 'It's always just me' has disappeared.
あんなに悲しい別れでも
Even with such a sad parting,
時間が経てば忘れてく
I'll forget it as time goes by.
新しい人と並ぶ君は
You, standing next to someone new,
ちゃんとうまくやれているのかな
I wonder if you're getting along well.
もう顔も
Even your face,
見たくないからさ
I don't want to see it anymore.
変に連絡してこないでほしい
I want you to stop contacting me unexpectedly.
都合がいいのは変わってないんだね
You haven't changed how selfish you are, have you?
でも無視できずにまた少し返事
But I can't ignore you, so I reply a little again.
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness,
多分 今も 嫌いじゃないの
Maybe, even now, I don't hate them.
…いた
…was holding on
時間が経てば
As time passes
きっと
Surely
色褪せる
It will fade away
月灯りに魔物が揺れる
Demons sway in the moonlight
きっと私もどうかなってる
I must be losing my mind too
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float in the darkness
赤黄色の色が胸の奥
Red and yellow colors deep within my chest
ずっと貴方の名前を呼ぶ
I keep calling your name forever
好きという気持ちまた香る
The feeling of love becomes fragrant again
声も
Your voice
顔も
Your face
不器用なとこも
Even your clumsiness
全部
All of it
大嫌いだよ
I hate it so much
まだ枯れない花を
A flower that hasn't withered yet
君に添えてさ
Placing it by your side
ずっと
Forever
抱えてよ
Hold onto it
「大丈夫」と
Saying "I'm fine"
また嘘をついた
You lied again
無理してるの
You're pushing yourself
声でわかるよ
I can tell by your voice
バレてるんだよ
I already know
ダメなとこ
Your flaws
性格だって
Your personality too
違う貴方
You are different
だけど似てる
But we're similar
とこも意外と
in surprising ways
あって
we have them
共鳴
Resonance
すぐにしだんだ
It happened immediately
惹かれ
Drawn
合った私たち
to each other
不思議な
It's mysterious
この絆
this bond
なんだか照れなくて
Somehow I'm not shy about it
夢を語り明かそう
Let's talk about dreams
朝まで
until morning
私がね頑張れる理由
The reason I can do my best
そう
Yes
一人じゃないから
because I'm not alone
貴方が笑えば
If you smile
私もつられる
I smile too
隣合わせの心
Our hearts side-by-side
連鎖してるよ
are connected
時には歩幅が
Sometimes our pace
ズレてしまうけど
might be out of sync, but
二人
the two of us
呼吸揃えさ
will synchronize our breathing
未来へと
Towards the future
進んでいこう
let's move forward
どれくらいの時間かな
How much time has passed?
周りと比べて
Comparing with those around me
果てしないトラック戦と
With this endless track race
追いつけるの
can I catch up?
なんて弱気な日も
Even on such weak days
激励し続けてくれた
you kept encouraging me
貴方にいつも感謝
Always grateful to you
転んでも立ち上がる
Even if I fall, I'll stand up
いつでも
Always
夢を叶えたいんだ
I want to make my dreams come true
必ず
Definitely
こんなにね打ち込めるのは
The reason I can be this absorbed
そう仲間がいるから
Yes, is because I have friends
貴方の悩みは
As for your worries
私が寄り添う
I will stay close to them
心が疲れたなら
If your heart gets tired
休憩しよう
let's take a break
遠慮はしないで
Don't hold back
そんな仲じゃない
we're not strangers
二人
The two of us
肩を組んでほら
look, with arms around each other
何度でも乗り越える
we'll overcome it again and again
世界中が敵になっても
Even if the whole world turns against me,
変わらずあなたの味方
I'll always be on your side.
右と
Right and
左
Left,
友達の証だよって
Proof that we are friends.
強く固く
Strongly, tightly,
縛ったリボン
The ribbon we tied.
話題のドラマも
The trending dramas,
虹の出る空も
The sky with a rainbow,
掴み取る栄光も
And the glory we'll grasp,
一緒に見たい
I want to see them all together.
あなたが笑えば
If you smile,
私もつられる
I can't help but smile too.
隣り合わせの心
Our hearts, side by side,
連鎖してるよ
Are linked together.
いずれそれぞれの
Even if someday, on our separate
道を歩いても
Paths we walk,
共に
Together,
支えになろうさ
Let's support each other.
未来へと進んで行こう
Let's move forward into the future.
どこにいても二人三脚
Wherever we are, we're in this three-legged race.
Woo...
with you
うわーー！できた！
Whoa! We did it!
できたー！
We did it!
二度目だけど
It's the second time, though.
めっちゃもう忘れてたから
I totally forgot it already!
イェーイ！
Yay!
6周年！6！
6th Anniversary! Six!
え？そっちで？こっちじゃないの？
Eh? That way? Isn't it this way?
え？あ、こう？韓国はこうだよ。
Eh? Ah, like this? In Korea, it's like this.
あ、勉強になりました。ありがとうございます。
Ah, I learned something new. Thank you very much.
6はこうなんですね。
So six is like this, huh.
6！おめでとう！
Six! Congratulations!
ありがとー！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm happy!
そうなんですよ。実はこの前、つなのね...
That's right. Actually, recently, for your...
はい！
Yes!
記念ライブ...誕生日ね。
...commemorative live... birthday, right.
そう。
Right.
誕生日記念のライブにね、出させていただいたので、
I was allowed to appear in your birthday live, so,
今回は...
This time...
え、なんかさ、初めてなんだよね。
Eh, like, it's the first time, right?
そう！ホロライブのスタジオに来ましたーー！
Right! I came to the Hololive studio!
イェーーイ！
Yaaay!
うわーすごい！ええすごい！
Whoa, amazing! Eh, amazing!
イェーイ！ありがとう、わざわざ来てくれて。
Yay! Thanks for coming all this way.
そうなんだよね。
It is, isn't it.
初めて...吸っていきます。
First time... I'm going to soak it all in.
ホロライブのスタジオです。
It's the Hololive studio.
3Dでコラボしましたーー！ありがとうーー！
We did a 3D collab! Thank you!
ええ、ありがとう！
Eh, thank you!
こちらこそ！
Thank you too!
そして、なんと...2年ぶりですよ。
And, believe it or not... it's been two years.
そうなんだよね。
That's right.
そう、この「二人三脚」という曲をね、やらせていただいたんですけれども、
Right, we performed this song "Ninin Sankyaku",
トワのファーストソロライブの時に...
During my first solo live...
初めてやって。覚えてた？振り。
We did it for the first time. Did you remember the choreo?
いやもう...完全に忘れてた！
No, well... I totally forgot it!
でも分かる。いろんなのをやってくとね、こうね、忘れちゃうから。
But I get it. When you do so many things, you just forget.
しかも2年ぶりだし。
Plus it's been two years.
そう、忘れちゃったけど...
Yeah, I forgot it but...
前はさ、シークレットゲストだったじゃん。
Before, I was a secret guest, right.
うん。
Yeah.
はじ...なんかこう、サムネで私がいる！
Fir... like, I'm there in the thumbnail!
そう！いるーー！ってなって。
Right! Like, "She's there!"!
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
でも本当にね、あの...あの曲...
But really, um... that song...
あそこで終わりじゃなくてこうやってね、またできたのがすごい嬉しいので。
I'm super happy we could do it again like this, and didn't just end it there.
ありがとうございます、という...
So, thank you very much...
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
はい。
Yes.
えーということでね、なんかソロライブ...
So with that said, like, solo live...
の時にコラボした後、こうやって3Dでコラボすることなかったから、
We haven't collabed in 3D like this since that time,
今日は、えー皆さんで無料で今お届けしてるので！
So today, we're bringing this to everyone for free!
無料でーーす！
It's free!
はい！
Yes!
えーと...じゃあ写真タイムするか。
Umm... shall we do a photo time?
え？する？改めて？
Eh? We doing it? Officially?
どういうポーズがいいですか？
What kind of pose is good?
え？指を動かして...
Eh? Wiggle your fingers...
だっさ動き！
That move is so lame!
今の、今のこれ何？
Just now, what was that?
陰キャピース。
Loner peace sign.
可愛い...可愛くピースやってみてよ。
Cute... try doing a cute peace sign.
可愛い。
Cute.
え？何が可愛いの？
Eh? What's cute about that?
これ古い？古いピースじゃん。
Is this old? That's an old peace sign.
古いって言われない？大丈夫？
Won't people say it's old? Is it okay?
今の流行りは？
What's trendy now?
今の流行り何？
What is trendy now?
これは？これは？
How about this? This?
これは？え？どっちのかな？
This? Eh? Which one is it?
間違ってる？
Am I doing it wrong?
同じやつやってる。
We're doing the same one.
ね、やって。私も。私もやりたいです。
Hey, do it. Me too. I want to do it too.
おー！すごいすごいすごい！
Oh! Amazing amazing amazing!
だっさ！
So lame!
え？何？
Eh? What?
今...喜びのダンス。
That was... the joy dance.
え？あ、出た。
Eh? Ah, there it is.
アイドル。
Idol.
イェーーイ！
Yaaay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いっぱい撮ってねーー。
Take lots of photos--.
いっぱい撮ってね。ありがとう。
Take lots. Thank you.
え？
Eh?
なんだよおい。
What is it, hey.
え？ハート作るからさ...グーして。
Eh? I'm gonna make a heart, so... make a fist.
トワがグーのほう？
Towa is the fist one?
グーして。
Make a fist.
こう？
Like this?
あーー！ありがとうございます！
Ah--! Thank you very much!
なんだ？マンガ？
What's this? Manga?
マンガ。嬉しい。
Manga. I'm happy.
可愛いよ。
It's cute.
可愛いじゃない？
Isn't it cute?
あ、嬉しいです。
Ah, I'm happy to hear that.
なんかすごい...
It's just amazing...
はだけちゃってごめんなさいね。
Sorry for being so exposed.
トワちゃんにはないものを持ってるような気がしてすごい。
I feel like you have something Towa-chan doesn't, it's amazing.
やめてくださいよ。
Please stop that.
いや、でも別に何がとは言ってないんですけど。
No, but I didn't say *what* specifically.
あ、そうですか。
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうそうですか。
Oh, yeah, is that so?
はい、ということでね...
Yes, so anyway...
今日は本当に来てくれてありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for coming today.
こちらこそ。ありがとう。
My pleasure. Thank you.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
またね、コラボも...
Again, let's collab...
しましょう。
Let's do it.
しよう。
遊ぼう。
Let's play.
ということで、
So with that said,
以上！
That's all!
スナトワでした！
It was SunaTowa!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
頑張ってー！
Good luck!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
群れをはぐれて
Straying from the herd
夢を咥えた
Holding a dream in my mouth
それが最後に
I felt that would be
なる気がしたんだ
The last time
獣は素直
Beasts are honest
人に媚び舞いた
But I flirted with people
それが最後に
I felt that would be
なる気がしたんだ
The last time
不確かな夢叶えるのさ
I'll make the uncertain dream come true
約束の夜に
On the night of the promise
微かな風に願うのさ
Wishing on the faint wind
静寂の朝に
In the silence of the morning
遠い星の少年は
The boy from a distant star
その腕に約束の飾り
Has a promised decoration on his arm
まだ旅路の最中さ
Still in the middle of the journey
幻惑の園に
In the garden of bewitchment
霞んで消えた
Blurred and vanished
轍の先へ
Beyond the tracks
それが最後に
I felt that would be
なる気がしたんだ
The last time
古の夢を
Old dreams
紡ぎ直せば
If I spin them again
それが最後に
I felt that would be
なる気がしたんだ
The last time
劣等を蹴り抗うのさ
Kicking away inferiority and resisting
約束の前に
Before the promise
命綱はないのさ
There is no lifeline
サーカスの夜に
On the circus night
まだ旅路の最中さ
Still in the middle of the journey
あの場所に加速するさらに
Accelerating further to that place
雨上がりのシャンデリア
Chandelier after the rain
幻惑の園に
In the garden of bewitchment
Swish the Jack yo
Mess of smash, sweet trip a kiddie mean now
Call your seizure, clapping, kidding me now
Dive to blue sky
Call your seizure, so
Call your seizure, path
Impulse
Swish the Jack yo
Pass code a penetrate a best bit floor
Get deeper buzzer beat
Wanna buzz us beat, 'bout heat check
Pass code a gamma beat
Pass code a penetrate a best bit floor
Wanna buzz a beat
Just wanna buzz a beat
脳内更地に Extra pass
Extra pass to the empty brain
食わずの Rehab
Rehab without eating
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
The time has come to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinite spiral.
言い訳に聞こえた理由は
The reason that sounded like an excuse,
儚い未来 手繰り寄せた弱さ
Was the weakness that reeled in a fleeting future.
それを強さと履き違えている
You mistake that for strength.
憎い
Hateful,
醜い
Ugly,
月を隠すほどの
Enough to hide the moon.
黒く
Black,
淀む
Stagnant,
心
Heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here.
揺らいでる
Wavering,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
Connecting wills like flowers.
奪っていく
Snatching away,
嵐のように心を割く
Tearing the heart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
The time has come to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinite spiral...
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
生まれ落ちた運命を飲んで
Swallowing the fate I was born into,
背負った数の夢を覚えた
I remember the number of dreams I've shouldered.
爛れるほど心燃やす感情
Emotions that burn the heart until it festers.
憎い
Hateful,
醜い
Ugly,
世界を分かつほどの
Enough to divide the world.
怒り
Anger,
燃やす
Burning,
心
Heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here.
揺らいでる
Wavering,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
Connecting wills like flowers.
奪っていく
Snatching away,
嵐のように心を割く
Tearing the heart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
The time has come to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinite spiral...
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
鬼哭に耳を傾けてしまえよ
Prick up your ears to the wailing,
この身に宿れば万物化してしまえよ
If it dwells in this body, transform everything.
無下を達者に託したい世は悪
The world where I want to entrust the void to the skilled is evil.
人 命の輝きは幾千層に
People... the brilliance of life in thousands of layers,
祈りの瞬きが照らす様に
As the twinkle of prayer illuminates.
夜半に身を宿し解を吸い付けろ
Dwell in the dead of night and suck out the solution.
解を吸い付けろ
Suck out the solution.
枯らしていく
Wither away,
夢幻の夜に花を咲く
Blooming flowers in the infinite night.
繋いでいく
Connect,
嵐に種を撒いていく
Sowing seeds in the storm.
揺らいでる
Wavering,
花のように意思を繋ぐ
Connecting wills like flowers.
奪っていく
Snatching away,
嵐のように心を割く
Tearing the heart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
The time has come to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinite spiral...
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
以上、ゲストパートでした！
That concludes the guest part!
ゲストパートでした！イェーイ！
It was the guest part! Yaaaay!
はい！ということでたくさんのメンバーがね
Yes! So, many members...
お祝いしに来てくれました！やったー！
Came to celebrate! Yay!
そして、本日の六周...
And, today's 6th anni...
ロックフェスみたいなのをちょっとイメージしておりまして
I was imagining something like a rock festival,
ちょっとねダンスよりも 好きに動いてねのフリーの動きを多めにしてみたので
so rather than strict choreography, I included a lot of free movement to just move as we liked.
それぞれのゲストとトワちゃんのね 個性が出てるパフォーマンスになってるんじゃないかなと思います
I think the performances really show off the individuality of each guest and myself.
なので配信とかを見直して
So please rewatch the stream,
「え ここ癖出てるな」とか思いながらもう一回
and think, "Oh, that's a quirk right there," while you...
改めて見ていただけると嬉しいです
...watch it again. I'd be happy if you did.
そしてまだ！
And we're not done yet!
このあとも歌いますから
I'm going to sing more after this,
チャンネルはそのままで！
so don't change the channel!
で プチ告知させてもらいます
So, let me make a small announcement.
はい
Yes.
2ndソロライブで発表いたしました
As announced at my 2nd Solo Live,
『勇者パーティーを追放されたビーストテイマー、最強種の猫耳少女と出会う』というアニメの主題歌
the theme song for the anime "Yuusha Party wo Tsuihou Sareta Beast Tamer..."
『シルベ』のMVがこのあと
the MV for "Shirube"...
配信が終わり次第！
...will be uploaded as soon as this stream ends!
常闇トワチャンネルにて上がります！
It will go up on the Tokoyami Towa Channel!
めちゃくちゃいいMVになったので
It turned out to be an incredibly good MV,
ぜひぜひ見てください
so please, please watch it.
見ないと
If you don't watch it...
人生を...
...your life...
損したまでとはいかないかもしれないけど損するかもしれない！
You might not completely ruin your life, but it'll be a loss!
ぐらいです！
That's how good it is!
はい 気合を入れて作ってもらいました
Yes, we put a lot of effort into making it.
はい よろしくお願いいたします
Yes, please check it out.
そしてアニメはなんと！
And regarding the anime, believe it or not!
明日から放送開始！
Broadcast starts tomorrow!
楽しみー！
I'm so excited!
ぜひ見てね
Please watch it!
そして
And...
MVだけではありません
It's not just the MV.
ありません
No, it's not.
『シルベ』のなんと
For "Shirube", actually...
シングルCDが発売決定！
A Single CD release has been decided!
本日から！
Starting today!
予約できます！
You can pre-order it!
なんですが こちらのね詳細は配信の最後にまとめてお伝えするので
However, I'll give you all the details at the end of the stream,
ここもチャンネルはそのままで
so keep the channel right here.
そしてさらに！
And furthermore!
本日はね 周年記念なので
Since today is my anniversary,
グッズの
regarding merchandise...
お知らせもあります！
...there is an announcement too!
もちろん！
Of course!
はい こちらの詳細もえー後でまた
Yes, I'll tell you the details about this later as well...
お伝えしますので
...so...
チャンネルはそのままで
...don't change the channel.
今日のキーワードは「チャンネルはそのままで」
Today's keyword is "Don't change the channel."
えーそしてね
Um, and also...
メン限のミニライブも今日はありますので
There's also a members-only mini-live today,
ぜひメンバーシップに入っていただけたら嬉しくて
so I'd be happy if you joined the membership and...
チャンネルはそのままで
...didn't change the channel.
どんだけ言うんだよって
Like, how many times am I gonna say it?
はい ということでありがとうございました
Yes, so thank you very much.
はい じゃあ最後にね一曲歌ってから告知しようかなと思うので
Okay, so I think I'll sing one last song before the announcements,
聴いてください
so please listen.
最後の一曲『シルベ』
The last song, "Shirube".
Watch your back! Warning!
ああ 隣り合わせで
Ah, side by side.
May God bless you!
言葉の綾ね
Figures of speech.
Warning! Warning!
彷徨いながら
While wandering,
I will stay true to myself 'cause of you
「はじめから」みたいに
Like "from the beginning",
何もない世界に
into a world with nothing,
理不尽 囚われる
captured by unreasonableness.
黙ってしまうほどの恐怖はない
There is no fear enough to silence me.
使い捨てるみたいに
Like throwing something away,
手を離したあなたに
to you who let go of my hand.
昨日とはまるで違う
It's completely different from yesterday.
わかったところでしょうがない
Even if I understood, it wouldn't help.
変わっていく身体と
My changing body,
心の中で響くVoice
and the Voice echoing in my heart.
間違ってなかったと
That I wasn't wrong...
ただこの空を眺めて
...I just gaze at this sky.
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time they overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
I end up remembering it all.
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I try to hide it is...
確かにあった後悔から
...because of the regret that was certainly there.
誓ったはずなんだ
I should have sworn it.
さよならすらシルベにしよう
Let's turn even goodbyes into a signpost.
光に触れる度 願ってしまうように
Just like how I wish every time I touch the light.
And still I rise
染まっていく
Being dyed in color.
必要もない
There's no need.
越えられないborder
A border that cannot be crossed.
揺れる意志をconvert
Convert the wavering will.
嘘で染めるような日々じゃ
In days colored by lies,
振り返った時にはheartache
there's only heartache when looking back.
まだ夜が明けるWake up
The dawn is breaking again, Wake up.
夢の中のflavor
The flavor inside a dream.
誰もいなくなった道を歩いてる
Walking down a road where everyone has gone.
今の私に
To the current me,
迷いすら重ねてくる
even hesitation piles up.
おとぎ話の正体
The true nature of the fairy tale.
誤魔化しきれなかった心が纏う熱を
The heat worn by a heart that couldn't be fully hidden,
憧れが照らしてる
is illuminated by longing.
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time they overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
I end up remembering it all.
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I try to hide it is...
大人になった後悔から
...because of the regret of becoming an adult.
月明かりの夜は
On moonlit nights,
さよならすらシルベにしよう
let's make even 'goodbye' a guidepost.
光を繋ぐたび
Each time we connect the light,
浮かぶ星座のように
like constellations floating above,
選んできた道のりを今を
the path we chose, and this moment...
いずれ後悔してしまう時が来ても
even if a time comes when we regret it,
私はまだ止まらない
I still won't stop.
夜空に浮かぶ月の光を
The moonlight floating in the night sky,
見上げた空に散らばる星の
the star's...
宝石を
...jewels scattered in the sky we looked up at.
道標にして
Making them my guidepost,
帰る場所
a place to return to.
重なってくたび
Every time they overlap,
思い出してしまうのに
I end up remembering,
誤魔化してしまうのは
yet what I try to gloss over is...
確かにあった後悔から
...because of the regret that certainly existed,
誓ったはずなんだ
I should have sworn.
さよならすらシルベにしよう
Let's make even 'goodbye' a guidepost.
光に触れるたび願ってしまうように
Just as I wish every time I touch the light.
And still I rise!!
染まってく必要もない
There's no need to be dyed by it.
どれも哀を模して
Imitating sorrow in everything,
true
はい ということで
Okay, so...
常闇トワ6周年記念ライブを見ていただきましてありがとうございました
thank you for watching Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
もうノンストップで
I brought it to you non-stop...
お届けしてまいりましたがいかがだったでしょうか
...but how was it?
たくさんね タグを使って
I'm waiting for lots of...
感想コメントを待っております
...impression comments using the tag!
ということで このあとは
So, after this,
お知らせをさせていただきたいと思います
I'd like to make some announcements.
まず1つ目
First one!
さっき歌った「シルベ」を収録した
The release of the single containing 'Shirube'...
シングルの発売が決定しました
...which I just sang, has been decided!
イェーイ
Yay!
今回のジャケット写真は
This time's jacket photo...
Graph77さんに書き下ろしていただきました
...was drawn by Graph77-san!
3月25日発売で
It goes on sale March 25th,
今回も全国流通での発売となります
and this time too, it will be a nationwide distribution release.
イェーイ
Yay!
そしてなんとカップリングには
And believe it or not, in the coupling,
「Present Day」のライブバージョンが入ります
the 'Present Day' live version will be included!
ユアネスさん繋がりということでね
It's because of the Yourness-san connection, you know.
「Present Day」はソロライブ 常闇トワ2ndライブの
'Present Day' uses the audio from...
音源を使用した
...the solo live, Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live.
楽曲が収録されておりますので
Since that track is recorded,
楽しみにしておいてください
please look forward to it!
はい そして今回は
Yes, and this time,
完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種をご用意しております
we have prepared two types: a fully limited production edition and a regular edition.
ということで こちらドン
So, here it is, boom.
完全生産限定盤には
The fully limited production edition...
オリジナルTシャツが入っております
...contains an original T-shirt.
今回の「シルベ」のジャケットイラストを使った
It's an original T-shirt using...
オリジナルTシャツとなっております
...the jacket illustration of 'Shirube' this time.
通常盤には初回プレス限定特典として
The regular edition contains, as a first press limited bonus,
ジャケットイラストステッカーが入ってます
a jacket illustration sticker.
ステッカーもね スマホに入れたり
I'd be happy if you put the sticker in your smartphone,
アケコンやパソコンとかに
or stuck it on your Arcade Controller or PC,
貼ってもらえたら嬉しいなと思ってます
or something like that.
はい こちらは本日21時から予約開始なんですが
Yes, this starts pre-order from 21:00 today, but...
なんとホロライブ公式ECでは
Surprisingly, on the Hololive official EC site,
この配信中にCDが
you might be able to buy the CD...
買えるようになってるかも
...during this stream!
ということで楽しみに待っててください
So please look forward to it,
チェックしてね
and check it out!
はい そして2つ目なんですが
Yes, and the second thing is...
常闇トワ活動6周年記念ライブグッズ
Tokoyami Towa Activity 6th Anniversary Live Goods...
あ ライブじゃねえわ
Ah, not live...
グッズ
Goods!
が発売いたします
...will be released!
イェーイ
Yay!
今回は数量限定盤もありますので
There is a limited quantity edition this time too,
ぜひチェックしてみてください
so please definitely check it out.
ということで 気になる内容は
So, the content you're curious about is...
こちらドン
...here, boom!
活動6周年記念フルセット こんな感じになっております
The Activity 6th Anniversary Full Set looks like this.
では細かく見ていきましょう
So let's look in detail.
まず1つ目はこちら
First is this.
「Towavelしてね」アクリルジオラマスタンド
'Towavel with me' Acrylic Diorama Stand.
イラストは大熊まい先生に描いていただきました
The illustration was drawn by Ookuma Mai-sensei.
ちょっとね 大人っぽいトワちゃんと一緒に
I hope you can go on a sort of date...
あのデート的なのいってもらえればなと思います
...with a slightly mature Towa-chan.
いつもね Towavelみんなしてくれて
Thank you everyone...
ありがとうございます
...for always doing Towavel.
これね あの本体をね
This, you know, you take out the main body...
こう取り出して
...like this...
ま 本体ってトワのことなんだけど
(Well, main body means Towa though)
トワを取り出して一緒にね
Take Towa out, and since I made the pose...
写真が撮れるポージングにしてるので
...so you can take photos together,
ぜひ一緒にね Towavelしてポストしてみてね
please definitely Towavel together and try posting it.
はい では次はこちら
Okay, next is this.
「トワとお揃い！？ジャージ」
'Matching Jersey with Towa!?'
トワのね 通常衣装の服をイメージした
It's a jersey imaging Towa's regular outfit clothes.
ジャージとなっております
It's become a jersey.
これね あのトワと全く一緒にすると
If I made this exactly the same as Towa's,
とんでもない露出度になるので
it would be an outrageous level of exposure, so...
長めの着やすい
Longer, easy to wear...
伝えております。
...conveying that.
よかったー。
Thank goodness.
ちゃんと裏地もね、ネオンピンクみたいな形の...
The lining is also properly, like a neon pink shape...
形じゃないね、ネオンピンク色になってますから
Not shape, it's a neon pink color.
本当にトワ様を、になっちゃったみたいなジャージになってます。
It's a jersey where you can really embody Towa-sama.
ちょっと大きめのサイズなんで、みんな着やすいのかなと思います。
Since the size is a bit large, I think it'll be easy for everyone to wear.
はい、ということで、じゃあ最後3つ目。
Okay, so, the last third item.
ビビハンドストラップ！
Bibi Hand Strap!
やっぱね、結構あのトワのジャージとかは、
You know, Towa's jersey and such are quite...
結構あの「The Goods」というかさ、キャラグッズみたいな感じするんですけれども
...well, very 'The Goods,' or feel like character goods, but...
通常使いもね、しやすいような...
I thought I wanted goods that are easy to use daily...
使い勝手の良いような、グッズも欲しいなと思いまして
...and practical to use, so...
ハンドストラップを作ってみました。
I tried making a hand strap.
イェイ。
Yay.
えー、カラーリングもね、すごい落ち着いていて
The coloring is also very calm...
トワっぽい色になったんじゃないかなと思うので、ぜひ購入お願いいたします。
...and I think it became a Towa-like color, so please buy it.
えーこちら、スマートフォンの画像はついておりますが、スマートフォンはついてきませんので
Uh, here, the image of the smartphone is attached, but the smartphone is not included...
よろしくお願いいたします。
...so please understand.
よろしくおねがいします（笑）
Please understand (lol).
はい、でこちらのね、セットを、えーご購入してくださった方には
Yes, and for those who purchased this set...
え... 笑顔のトワの...
Uh... smiling Towa's...
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
A foil-stamped reproduction signature Cheki-style bromide card is included.
はい、でそしてね、数量限定で直筆サイン入り
Yes, and also, in limited quantities, with a handwritten signature...
こちら直筆サインで、えー... お渡し...
This is a handwritten signature, um... to hand over...
したいなと思っておりますので
...is what I'd like to do, so...
ぜひどっちも手に入れてくれればなと思います。
I hope you can get both.
かわいい！
Cute!
よろしくお願いいたします。
Thank you.
ということで、以上こんな感じで
So, that's it, like this...
常闇トワ6周年記念のグッズの紹介でした！
It was the introduction of Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Goods!
え、フルセットね、常闇トワのグッズ、両方よろしくお願いいたします。
Um, the full set and Tokoyami Towa's goods, please support both.
ということで今日は見てくれてありがとう！
So, thank you for watching today!
このあとはメン限でライブしますから
After this, I'll do a live for members only...
ぜひよろしくお願いいたします！
So please definitely join!
イェイ！
Yay!
じゃあね、メンバーシップ加入と、グッズ購入と全部よろしくね。
See ya, please join membership, buy goods, and everything!
あけおめ！バイバイ！
Happy New Year! Bye bye!